AWS region is a geographically separated portion of the AWS global infrastructure.
AWS 区域是 AWS 全球基础设施的地理分隔部分
This geographic separation can help your platform
这种地理隔离可以帮助您的平台
continue to operate through a wide array of conditions,
继续通过各种各样的条件运作
including major internet disruptions or natural disasters.
包括重大的互联网干扰或者自然灾害
Each region is separated from the others by hundreds of miles.
每个区域都以  英里的距离与其他区域隔开
They are isolated so that they are not interdependent,
它们是孤立的 使它们不是相互依存的
but they are connected by a global high-speed,
但它们是由全球高速连接的
high bandwidth private AWS network.
高带宽专用 AWS 网络
Regions are also highly useful when dealing with personal,
区域在处理个人问题时也非常有用
health, or financial data,
健康或财务数据
where local governments may have
地方政府可能有
data locality laws requiring that citizen data is not stored in other countries.
数据位置法 要求公民数据不存储在其他国家或地区
Today, there are more than 20 regions spread around the world
今天 全球有 20 多个地区分布
and terabits or multiple terabits of bandwidth between regions.
以及区域间带宽的多个特差
AWS has a global private fiber network with redundant paths.
AWS 拥有一个具有冗余路径的全球专用光纤网络
AWS has complete control over this network.
AWS 已完全控制此网络
Creating applications that run actively in multiple regions at the same time,
创建在多个区域中同时运行的应用程序
provides for global redundancy and fast delivery to local users.
为本地用户提供全球冗余和快速交付
An active multi-region application has data and services
活动的多区域应用程序具有数据和服务
spread throughout the world and can be resilient to most types of service interruption.
并可抵御大多数类型的服务中断
A well-constructed multi-region application is,
一个精心构建的多区域应用是
pick a catchphrase, world-class,
选一个时髦的世界一流的
enterprise grade, industrial strength.
企业等级 工业强度
You have access on AWS to build the highest tier of reliable,
您可以访问 AWS 以建立最高级别的可靠
available, and resilient platforms.
以及弹性平台
Before Public Clouds, this level of performance
在公共云之前 此级别的性能
was only available to multi-billion dollar companies.
只能供  美元的公司使用
Running in multiple regions is completely optional.
在多个区域中运行是完全可选的
In fact, if you don't intentionally try to,
事实上如果你不刻意去尝试
you'll only be running in one region.
你只会在一个地区跑
Most AWS services must be managed on a per region basis.
大多数 AWS 服务必须按地区进行管理
When you create resources in one region,
在一个区域中创建资源时
it does not exist in the other regions.
它在其他区域不存在
There are a few exceptions to this,
有几个例外
and they are the AWS,
他们是 AWS
global services such as IAM,
全球服务 如 IAM
where identity and access management must span the entirety of AWS.
其中身份和访问管理必须跨越 AWS 的全部
Another example is Cloudfront,
另一个示例是 Cloudfront
where the primary goal of the service is to distribute data globally.
服务的主要目标是在全球分发数据
S3 is also a global service,
S3 也是一个全球性的服务
and that every region is displayed at once in the AWS console,
每个区域都在 AWS 控制台中显示一次
but an S3 bucket still lives in a single region.
但 S3 桶仍然生活在一个区域
One reason for this is that there is
原因之一是
typically some amount of additional costs to run a multiple regions.
通常会有一些额外的成本来运行多个区域
You must determine if your use case warrants the cost and complexity.
您必须确定您的用例是否需要成本和复杂性
As AWS build services,
作为 AWS 构建服务
they generally released them at first to only some
他们一般都是先放了一些
regions.This allows AWS to slowly bring
允许 AWS 缓慢地
some users onto a service.This is
某些用户在服务上 这是
another example of how AWS regions are managed independently.
AWS 区域如何独立管理的另一个示例
Make sure that a service is available and all
确保服务可用且所有
of the regions you utilize before adopting that service.
在采用该服务之前所使用的区域
Database console shows you which region you're currently working in,
数据库控制台显示您当前正在使用的区域
in the upper right-hand corner.
在右上角
You also need to specify a region when you work with the AWS CLI or an AWS SDK,
您还需要在使用 AWS CLI 或 AWS SDK时指定区域
if you find yourself suddenly missing several resources,
如果你发现自己突然失去了几个资源
make sure you're looking at the correct region.
确保你看到的是正确的区域
On occasion, the AWS counsel can accidentally switch regions on you.
有时  AWS 大律师可以意外地切换您的区域